Narrator: 1
M: I think we need to prioritize discussing the budget, as it’s currently more urgent.
Narrator: 2
M: To scientists’ surprise,
the 30-year study revealed no correlation between a vegan diet and good health.
Narrator: 3
M: The writer claims to be the first to investigate this connection.
Narrator: 4
M: The popularity of live TV has significantly decreased over the last ten years,
as people move to streaming services.
Narrator: 5
M: The study has concluded that a larger brain doesn’t necessarily make an animal more intelligent.
Narrator: 6
F: After years of steady improvement,
driving test pass rates peaked at 60%, and have been dropping over the past few years.
Narrator: 7
F: We’re expecting house prices to rise by approximately 7%, but then to fall again.
Narrator: 8
F: Before we publish the results in our paper, we will need to analyse our research in detail.